A Finding Aid to the Erwin Panofsky Papers, 1904-1990 (bulk dates 1920-1968), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Printed Material, 1904-1990, undated; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; (Box 19; 0.5 linear ft.)
  - Reviews of Panofsky's Writings, Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Meaning in the Visual Arts, 1955-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - A Mythological Painting by Poussin, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Pandora's Box [with Dora Panofsky], 1956-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Renaissance and Renascences, 1960-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Tomb Sculpture, 1964-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 31)